navarre.com 2014-04-27

# Speed Commerce

We recognize that you care how information about you is collected and used. Our Online Privacy Policy has been developed to guide us in the collection and use of information about visitors to this web site while respecting their privacy rights. 

GENERAL

Speed Commerce, Inc. is committed to privacy and data protection and has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy rights. This Speed Commerce, Inc. Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") is intended to tell you about the type of information that is collected on this web site ("Site") and how such information is used.

By using our Site, you consent to the collection, use, and storage of your information by Speed Commerce, Inc. in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you should cease use of this Site immediately. 

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE 

Voluntary Submission of Personal Information.In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, you may choose to give us personal information, such as your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you or to allow you to participate in features offered by this Site. If at any time you wish to have your name removed from a mailing list, subscription or other direct mailing you may receive from us, send us an email at [privacy@speedcommerce.com](mailto:privacy@speedcommerce.com) and we will remove your name promptly.

Automatic Collection of Information and Use of Cookies.

This Site may automatically collect certain information such as the Internet address of the domains from which users visit us and may analyze this data for trends and statistics. Also, when you access this Site, we may store information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of text stored on your computer that may, for example, help us know which browser you are using and where you have been on our Site. A cookie may also tell us which pages are being viewed and which are not. This information helps us to improve the Site. Our Site does not require visitors to accept cookies, although some features of the Site may not be available to users who do not accept cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored and you can erase cookies from your computer.

Retention and Use of Information by Speed Commerce, Inc.

Unless otherwise disclosed herein or during the collection, personally identifiable information that may be collected from visitors to this Site is retained by Speed Commerce, Inc. Speed Commerce, Inc. does not sell or transfer personal information collected on this Site to outside parties except to agents or contractors of Speed Commerce, Inc. for business-related purposes in connection with services of this Site or of Speed Commerce, Inc. We may disclose aggregate statistics using information collected on our Site, but such statistics will include no personally identifiable information. Resumes and related information submitted on this Site by applicants for employment may be distributed to Speed Commerce, Inc. and its agents for recruiting or other employment-related purposes. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Speed Commerce, Inc. may release information when we believe that such release is necessary to (i) comply with applicable law or governmental authorities, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our agreements or (iii) protect the security or integrity of this Site or the rights, property or safety of Speed Commerce, Inc. or others. 

Submission of Information by Children.

Speed Commerce, Inc. has no intention of collecting any personal data from children (under thirteen years of age). Whenever appropriate, Speed Commerce, Inc. will specifically instruct children not to submit personal information on this Site. Additionally, if we receive such information from children, we will delete the information as soon as we discover it or we will take reasonable and appropriate steps to ensure parental consent to such submission. 

Parents should be aware that this Policy will govern our use of personal data collected on this Site, but that information which is voluntarily given by children in chat sessions, email exchanges, bulletin boards or the like may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited contact. Speed Commerce, Inc. encourages all parents to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their personal data while using the Internet. 

Parents may review any personal information collected at this Site about their children, and require that the information be deleted. However, since Speed Commerce, Inc. does not seek to collect any personal information about children, and we delete such information that we collect inadvertently as soon as we discover that a child has submitted it, we generally retain no information about children that could be reviewed or deleted. In the rare event in which a parent requests review or deletion of information about his or her child before we have discovered and deleted the information, then Speed Commerce, Inc. will promptly comply with that request.

SECURITY OF INFORMATION 

Speed Commerce, Inc. uses commercially reasonable efforts to store and maintain personal information to protect it from loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction by any unauthorized use. While we strive to protect your personal information, Speed Commerce, Inc. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

LINKS TO OTHER SITES 

Please be aware that we provide links to other websites as a convenience to visitors to this Site and such third-party sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Neither Speed Commerce, Inc. nor this Site is responsible for the content or information collection practices of any third-party linked site. 

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

Speed Commerce, Inc. reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. You should visit this page from time to time to review the then-current Privacy Statement because they are binding on you. This Privacy Policy was last updated in April 24, 2009. 

FOR MORE INFORMATION

Questions about this Privacy Policy may be directed to Speed Commerce, Inc. at [privacy@speedcommerce.com](mailto:privacy@speedcommerce.com).
